<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<translate>
    <name>group</name>
    <!-- define the block title translations -->
    <title_add>Add New Group</title_add>
    <title_update>Update Group</title_update>
    <title_view>View Groups</title_view>
    <title_search>Search Groups</title_search>
    <!-- define the menu lable translations -->
    <menu>Groups</menu>
    <menu_add>Add</menu_add>
    <menu_view>List</menu_view>
    <menu_search>Search</menu_search>
    <!-- define the field translations -->
    <field_date_orig>Date of Creation</field_date_orig>
    <field_date_start>Date of Activation</field_date_start>
    <field_date_expire>Date of Expiration</field_date_expire>
    <field_name>Name</field_name>
    <field_notes>Notes</field_notes>
    <field_status>Active</field_status>
    <field_pricing>Allow Alternate Pricing?</field_pricing>
    <field_parent_id>Parent Group</field_parent_id>
    <!-- define the help file -->
    <help_file><![CDATA[
        Groups are simply a set of permissions that accounts can be authorized for. Each
        group is simply a list of methods that accounts associated with the group can access.
        <BR><BR>
        For example, if a particular group is authorized for the Account Administration methods, any account
        authorized for that group can access the  Account Administration features.
        <BR><BR>
        The group configuration is very flexible. For example, a group can have access to only some of the
        methods in a specific module. So, group(s) can be define for employees that allow them to
        view and search for accounts, but not to delete or edit them.
        <BR><BR>
        The group hierarchy also allows for up to three levels of groups, so a parent group can be defined, 
        and each unlimited child groups can be defined under that parent group. Those 2nd tier child groups can then have children of their
        own. The advantage of this system is that the child group(s) always inherit all it's parents
        permissions, and then you can add additional permissions to the child. This makes it
        possible to very quickly create a group that has all the permissions of an existing group,
        plus a few changes.
        <BR><BR>
        The group hierarchy is show above this help dialogue.
        ]]></help_file>
    <!-- define any custom resources -->
    <select_module>Select a module</select_module>
    <title_visual>Group Layout Visualization</title_visual>
    <title_relation>Update Group to Method Relationships</title_relation>
</translate>